Washington Star 061 061
Stage
- Series 23: Photograph Morgue
  - Sub-Series 1: Biographical
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Piano) - Nixon, Richard M. (Planes and Helicopters) (Box 1019)
    - Nixon (Planting Trees) - Nixon (Portraits) (Box 1020)
    - Nixon (Prizes & Awards) - Nixon (Resignation) (Box 1021)
    - Nixon (Recreation) - Nixon (Mrs. w/Groups) (Box 1022)
    - Nixon (Signing Treaties) - Nixon (Speaking 1969) (Box 1023)
    - Nixon (Planting Trees) - Nixon (Portraits) (Box 1024)
    - Nixon (St. Patrick's Day) - Nixon (Signing Legislator) (Box 1025)
    - Nixon (Speaking 1974) (Box 1026)
    - Nixon (Speaking State & Union - Telephoning) (Box 1027)
    - Nixon (Thanksgiving Day - Vice President) (Box 1028)
    - Nixon (Vice President - Visits Austria 1972) (Box 1029)
    - Nixon (Visits Azores - Visits CIA) (Box 1030)
    - Nixon Visits China (Box 1031)
    - Nixon (Visits China 1972 - Visits England) (Box 1032)
    - Nixon (Visits England 1978 - Europe - Italy) (Box 1033)
    - Nixon (Europe 1970 - Visits France 1974) (Box 1034)
    - Nixon (Visits Louisana 1979 - Visits Middle East) (Box 1035)
    - Nixon (Visits Georgia - Visits Lincoln Memorial) (Box 1036)
    - Nixon (Visits Midway - Visits Russia) (Box 1037)
    - Nixon Visits Russia (Box 1038)
    - Nixon (Visits School - Visits World - India) (Box 1039)
    - Nixon (Visits World - Pakistan - White House Tour) (Box 1040)
    - Nixon (White House Portraits - Press Conference 1974) (Box 1041)
    - Nixon (With Actors - With Ambassadors) (Box 1042)
    - Nixon (With Ambassadors - With Chinese (Box 1043)
    - Nixon (With Congressman - With Ford) (Box 1044)
    - Nixon (With Foreign Dignitaries - With Groups) (Box 1045)
    - Nixon (With Groups) - Nkrumah, Kwane (Box 1046)
    - Nixon (With Groups - Indians) (Box 1047)
    - Nixon (With Johnson - With Pompidou) (Box 1048)
    - Nixon (With Poster Children - With Trudeau) (Box 1049)
    - Nixon (With Trudeau) - Nixon (Mrs. Health) (Box 1050)
    - Nixon, Richard (General - 1958) (Box 1051)
    - Nixon (1959 - With Aides Haldeman) (Box 1052)
    - Nixon (1973 - Biographical) (Box 1053)
    - Nixon Coins - Demonstrations (Box 1054)
    - Nixon (Dress and Fashion) - Florida (Box 1055)
    - Nixon (Funerals - Hair) (Box 1056)
    - Nixon (Unsorted) (Box 1057)
    - Nixon (Unsorted) (Box 1058)
    - Nobel, Alfred - Wolan, Kathy (Box 1059)
    - Nolu, Richard - Norris, Johanna (Box 1060)
    - Norris, Kathi - Norvell, Aubrey (Box 1061)
    - Norway, Royal Family - Novak, Michael (Box 1062)
    - Noak, Robert - Nugent, Patrick (Mrs.) (Box 1063)
    - Nugent, Patrick (Mrs.) - Nwoko Demos (Box 1064)
    - Nuxhall, Joe - Obenshain, Richard (Box 1065)
    - Oberdorfer, Lou - O'Brien Twins (Box 1066)
    - O'Brien, Edmond - O'Brien, Margaret (Box 1067)
    - O'Brien, Margaret - O'Connell, Thomas (Box 1068)
    - O'Connor, Alden - O'Connor, William (Box 1069)
    - O'Daniel, W. Lee - O'Donohue, Martin (Box 1070)
    - O'Donoghue, Joseph - Ogilly, Angus (Box 1071)
    - Ogilly, Richard - O'Hara, John (Box 1072)
    - O'Hara, Maureen - Ojuwu, C.O. (Box 1073)
    - Okada, Keisuke - Olds, Robin (Box 1074)
    - Oleary, Brian - Oliver, Ed (Box 1075)
    - Oliver, Gene - Olmstead, George (Box 1076)
    - Olmstead, George - O'Malley, Walter (Box 1077)
    - Oman, Sulten - Onassis, Aristole (Box 1078)
    - Onassis, Aristole (Mrs.) (Box 1079)
    - Onassis, Aristole (Mrs.) - Onassis, Tina (Box 1080)
    - O'Neal, Daniel - O'Neil, Steve (Box 1081)
    - O'Neil, Thomas - Opperman, Jan (Box 1082)
    - Orantes, Manuel - Orlov, Yun (Box 1083)
    - Ormandy, Eugene - Ortiz, Roberto (Box 1084)
    - Ortona, Egidio - Osmond, Donny & Marie (Box 1085)
    - Osmond Brothers - Oswald, Lee Harvey (Box 1086)
    - Oswald, Lee Harvey - Oulu, James P. Jr. (Box 1087)
    - Ourisman, Mandell - Owens, Hugh F. (Box 1088)
    - Owens, Jesse - Ozers, Marite (Box 1089)
    - Paar, Jack - Pack, Rod (Box 1090)
    - Packard, David - Page, Roberta (Box 1091)
    - Page, Rodney J. - Pakala, Alan (Box 1092)
    - Palacio, Alfredo - Olof, Palme (Box 1093)
    - Palmer, Alison - Palmer, Roberta (Box 1094)
    - Palmer, Sandra - Panyushkin, Alexandra (Box 1095)
    - Pao, Vang - Paquet, Wilfred (Box 1096)
    - Parks, Andy - Parlar, Roberta (Mrs.) (Box 1097)
    - Parker, Salty - Parks, Thomas (Box 1098)
    - Parlin, Charles - Parnu, Loretta (Box 1099)
    - Paraskevopoulos, John - Park, Jong Sun (Box 1100)
    - Parseghian, Ara - Parzow, Hilliams (Box 1101)
    - Pasarell, Charlie - Pastor, Laszlo (Box 1102)
    - Pate, Corpl. Arlie - Paton, Jean (Box 1103)
    - Patrese, Ricardo - Patterson, Pat (Box 1104)
    - Patterson, Raymond - Putulski, Walt (Box 1105)
    - Pauker, Anna - Pavarotti, Luciano (Box 1106)
    - Pavel, Josef - Paz, Octavio (Box 1107)
    - Peay, Larry - Peel, Joseph (Box 1108)
    - Peabody, Eddie - Pearle, John (Box 1109)
    - Peau, Richard - Pease, James (Box 1110)
    - Peel, Roy - Pell, Claiburn (Box 1111)
    - Pel - Pen (Box 1112)
    - Pennel, John - Peppler, Joseph P. (Box 1113)
    - Pera, Steven - Pery, Sharon (Box 1114)
    - Pereiva, Albery - Perkins, Carols (Box 1115)
    - Perkins, Cy - Perkinson, Pat (Mrs.) (Box 1116)
    - Perle, Richard - Perpich, Rudy (Box 1117)
    - Perranoskii, Ron - Perry, Williams (Box 1118)
    - Pershey, Marta - Peters, Gail (Box 1119)
    - Peters, Hank - Peterson, Paul (Box 1120)
    - Peterson, Barbara - Peterson, Randolph (Box 1121)
    - Peterson, Russell - Petska, Cheryl (Box 1122)
    - Petterie, Lucia - Phelan, James (Box 1123)
    - Phelan James (writer) - Phillips Howard (Ofiice of Economic Opportunity) (Collective Folders: PHI; PHILLIPS, PHILLIPS A1) (Box 1124)
    - Phillips, Jess (Sports) - Phuomng Tran Kim ( S Vietnam AMB. To US 1972) (Collective Folders: PHILLIPS, JR; PHILLIPS, S ) (Box 1125)
    - Piaf, Edith (Deceased) - Picasso, Paloma (Collective Folders: PI; PIC) (Box 1126)
    - Picard, Prof. August - Pidgeon, Walter (Actor) (Collective Folders: PICK) (Box 1127)
    - Pieck, Wilhelm - Pignatano, Joe Baseball (Brooklyn Dodgers) (Collective Folders: PIE;PIER, PIER; PIERCE, PIG) (Box 1128)
    - Pihl, Paul E and Mrs. - Pinchot, Gifford lll (Grandson of Fomer PA Gov) (Collective Folders: PIL; PIN) (Box 1129)
    - Pinci, Gianna - Pinza, Enzio (Singer Deceased) (Collective Folders: PINK) (Box 1130)
    - Pio, Padre - Pittle R David (Consumer Safety Product Comm) (Collective Folders: PIO; PIP, PIR; PIS; PITT) (Box 1131)
    - Pitman, Beatrice Thayer Mrs (Christian Science Teacher) - Platzer Wilifred DR (Austrian AMB to US 1958) (Collective Folders: PIT; PL) (Box 1132)
    - Player Gary (Golf) - Pliskow Barbara (Airplane Hijack Attempt) (Collective Folders: PLE; PLI) (Box 1133)
    - Ploen, Kenny (Football Player) - Podres Joh nny (Baseball) (Collective Folders: PLO; PLU; PO; POD) (Box 1134)
    - Poenish, Walter (Swimmer) - Polic Henry ll (Actor) (Collective Folders: POE; POF; POH, POL) (Box 1135)
    - Polinger, Milton (Builder Sportsman) - Pompiano, Paul (Realtor Builder) (Collective Folders: POLK, POLL) (Box 1136)
    - Pompidou, Georges - Pomraning, George L. Jr. (See: Murders - Policemen 1983) (Collective Folders: POM) (Box 1137)
    - Ponce, Camilio Enriquez (Ecuador President) - Pope, James S. (Collective Folders: PON; PONT; POO; POOL; POOLE; POOR; POP) (Box 1138)
    - Pope, John Alexander (Director - Freed Gallery) - Pope John Paul II (Box 1139)
    - Pope John Paul II - Pope John Paull II (Visits - Ireland 1979 (Box 1140)
    - Pope Jon Paull II (Visits Italy (Earthquake) - 1979 Visit to US) (Box 1141)
    - Pope Leo XIII - Pope, Phillip (U.S. Army) (Box 1142)
    - Pope, Sam ( Va. Del.) - Porter, Katherine Anne ( Author) (Box 1143)
    - Porter, Kenneth Jess - Posey, Sam (Auto Racer) (Collective Folders: POS) (Box 1144)
    - Post, Elizabeth - Potwin, Denis (Ice Hockey NHL) (Collective Folders: POST; POT) (Box 1145)
      Folders do not fill box and lean; curling issues?
    - Potter, Beatrix (Author) - Povich, Shirley (Columnist) (Collective Folders: POTT; POU) (Box 1146)
    - Powell, Adam Clayton - Powell, Enoch (MP) (Collective Folders: POW; POWELL A-I) (Box 1147)
    - Powell, James M. (Policeman) - Powell, William (Supreme Court Justice) (Collective Folders: POWELL J-R; POWELL S-Z) (Box 1148)
    - Powers, Jules (Actor) - Powers Stefanie (Actress) (Collective Folders: POWER;POWERS;POWERS JQ; POWERS S; POWERS T; POWERS UV) (Box 1149)
    - Powless, John (Coach) - Prefontaine, Steve (Track) (Collective Folders: POY; POZ; PR; PRAT; PRE) (Box 1150)
    - Preinkert, Alma - Presley, Elvis (Grave) (Collective Folders: PREI; PREN; PRES; PRESCOTT) (Box 1151)
    - Presley Elvis (Exhibit Materials) - Presley Vernon (Father of Elvis Presley Deceased) (Collective Folders: PRES; PREST; PREV) (Box 1152)
    - Presnell, Harve (Singer and Actor) - Preus Jacob A.O (Collective Folders: PREV; PRI; PRICE A; PRICE B; PRICE C; PRICE D; PRICE E, PRICE F;PRICE G; PRICE H; PRICE I; PRICE J; PRICE K) (Box 1153)
    - Prevatte, Billy Ray (Murders - MD Cameron Frazer) - Price Jim (Basketball Player) (Box 1154)
    - Price, Leontyne - Price, Winston DR (Scientist Cold Vaccine) (Collective Folders: PRICE L; PRICE M; PRICE N; PRICE O; PRICE P; PRICE Q; PRICE R; PRICE S; PRICE T; PRICE U; PRICE V; PRICE W; PRICE XYZ) (Box 1155)
    - Prideax, James (Playwright) - Prinz Dr. Joachim (Collective Folders: PRID; PRIE; PRIN) (Box 1156)
    - Prinze, Freddie (Actor) - Prosky, Robert (Actor) (Collective Folders: PRO; PRIT; PROC, PROCH, PROCTOR; PROS) (Box 1157)
    - Protho James Thompson Dr - Proxmire William Sen. - Wisconsin (Box 1158)
    - Proxmire, William (Hair) - Pugmire Kathryn (1969 Cherry Blossom Queen) (Collective Folders: PRU; PRY; PS; PU; PUC; PUG) (Box 1159)
    - Puhan, Alfred - Purim Flora (Singer) (Collective Folders: PUL; PUM; PUN; PUR; PURC; PURD) (Box 1160)
    - Purkey, Bob (Baseball Player) - Pyun Young Tai Dr (korea) (Collective Folders: PURVIS; PUT; PUTN) (Box 1161)
    - Qabus Sultan of Oman - Queen (Rock Group) (Collective Folders: Q; QUA; QUAN; QUAS; QUE; QUEEN) (Box 1162)
    - Queen, Roland J. (Forest Haven Adm.) - Quinlan, Kathleen (Collective Folders: QUI; QUIG; QUIL; QUIN) (Box 1163)
    - Quinn, Alice (Actress) - Qvale, Kjell (Sportsman) (Collective Folders: QUINN A-I; QUINN J-R; QUINN S-Z) (Box 1164)
    - Raab, Julius - Raczkewicz, Viladyslav (Collective Folders: R; RAB; RAC) (Box 1165)
    - Radatz, Dick (Baseball Player) - Read, Barbara (Actress) (Collective Folders: RAD; RADE; RADI; RADO; RAE) (Box 1166)
    - Rafael, Gideon (Israili Prime Minister) - Ramin, Haroon (Collective Folders: RAF; RAG; RAH) (Box 1167)
    - Raich, Eric (Baseball) - Ralston, Vera (Collective Folders: RAI; RAIN; RAJ; RAK; RAL) (Box 1168)
    - Ram, Jagjivan (India Official) - Ramsay, Gerrard (Football) (Collective Folders: RAM; RAMO; RAMS; RAMSAY; RAMSEY) (Box 1169)
    - Ramsey, Herbert P. Dr. - Randall, Sue (Actress) (Collective Folders: RAN; RAND; RANDALL) (Box 1170)
    - Randall, Theodore (Writer) - Rankin, W. Parkman ( V. P. This Week magazine) (Collective Folders: RANDOLPH; RANKIN A-Z) (Box 1171)
    - Rankovich, Alexsander (Yugoslavia Interior Minister) - Rasulala, Waltye (TV) (Collective Folders: RANS; RAO; RAP; RAS; RASM; RASK) (Box 1172)
    - Ratchford, William (Maryland Fiscal Adviser) - Ravnda, Christian M. (Collective Folders: RAT; RATT; RAU; RAV) (Box 1173)
    - Rawalt. Marguerite (National Business Women's Club) - Ray, Frank Edward (School Bus Driver) (Collective Folders: RAW; RAY; RAY A-K) (Box 1174)
    - Ray James Earl - Rayburn Sam (House Speaker) (Collective Folders: RAY) (Box 1175)
    - Raye, Martha (Singer Actress) - Reading is Fundamental (Collective Folders: RAYB; RAYE; RAYM; RAYN; RAYZ; RE; REA; READ) (Box 1176)
    - Reagan Danny - Reagan Assisination Attempt (Box 1177)
    - Reagan, Ronald (As Actor) - Reagan Ronald (General) (Collective Folders: REAM; REAV; REC; REDD; RED) (Box 1178)
    - Reagan Ronald (Cartoons) - Reagan Ronald (Plans) (Box 1179)
    - Reagan Ronald (Portraits Smiling) - Reagan Ronald (Telephone) (Box 1180)
    - Reagan Ronald (Visits University of California) - Reagan, Ronald (With Justices) (Box 1181)
    - Reagan Ronald (With Khachigian Ken) - DEC 1980 (Box 1182)
    - Reagan Ronald Mrs (Box 1183)
    - Reagan, Ronald (1981) - Reagan -TENN (Box 1184)
    - Reagan, Texas - With Groups (Box 1185)
    - Reaguer WH (Undertaker) - Reddy Tom (TV Quiz Show) (Collective Folders: REDE) (Box 1186)
    - Redfern Jim (soccer Player) - Redondo Maria (Tennis Player) (Collective Folders: REDM; REED A1; REE; REED JR) (Box 1187)
    - Reece B Carroll (Former Rep Chairman) - Redd Stanley F (Justice) (Box 1188)
    - Reed, Theodore H. (Acting Zoo Director) - Reeside, Harmer (Dutch) (Collective Folders: REED S-Z; REES; REESE) (Box 1189)
    - Reeves, Albert L. (Judge) - Rehnquist, William (Mrs.) (Collective Folders: REEVES; REG; REH) (Box 1190)
    - Reichardt, Paul E. (W G and L Official) - Reilly, John R. ( To Join PTC) (Collective Folders: REI; REICH; REID A-I; REID J-Q; REID R-Z; REIL; REILLY A-H; REILLY I-P; REILLY Q-Z) (Box 1191)
    - Reinartz, Frederick Eppling (Dr.) - Remenyi, Maria (Miss U.S.A. 1966) (Collective Folders: REIN; REINE; REIS; REIT; REM) (Box 1192)
    - Remick; Lee (Actress) - Renzi, Eva (Actress) (Collective Folders: REN; REND; RENE; RENN; RENS) (Box 1193)
    - Rentschler, William - Reuther, Walter (Collective Folders: REP; RES; RET; REU) (Box 1194)
    - Reuther, Walter ( President United Auto Workers) - Reynolds, Adeline DeWalt (Actress) (Collective Folders: REV; REY; REYNOLDS A-J) (Box 1195)
    - Reynolds, Hurt - Reynolds Sam W. (Collective Folders: REYNOLDS J-R; REYNOLDS S-Z) (Box 1196)
    - Reynolds, Thomas H. - Rhodes, Zandra (Collective Folders: RH; RHE; RHI; RHO; RHODES A-H; RHODES I-P; RHODES P-Z) (Box 1197)
    - Rhome, Jerry (Football Player) - Rice-Davies, Mandy (Party Girl) (Collective Folders: RI; RIB; RIC; RICE) (Box 1198)
    - Rich, Buddy - Richards, Vincent (Tennis) (Collective Folders: RICH; RICH A-H; RICH I-P; RICH Q-Z; RICHARD; RICHARDS I-P; RICHARDS Q-Z) (Box 1199)
    - Richardson, Al (Football NFL) - Richardson, Elliot (Mrs) (Collective Folders: RICHARDS A-H; RICHARDSON A-H) (Box 1200)
    - Richardson, Frederick W. (Mayor Mount Ranier) - Richert, Pete (Baseball Player) (Collective Folders: RICHARDSON I-P; RICHARDSON Q-Z; RICHE) (Box 1201)
    - Richey - Rickles (Box 1202)
    - Rickman Bob (Disc Jockey) - Riefensthal Leni (German Actress) (Collective Folders: RID) (Box 1203)
    - Riegel Skee (Golf) - Riggs Bobby (Football NFL) (Collective Folders: RIE; RIF; RIG) (Box 1204)
    - Riggs, Glen - Rinaldi, Kathy (Tennis) (Collective Folders: RIH; RIK; RIL; RIM) (Box 1205)
    - Rinehart, Rus - Rippy, Rodney Alan (Collective Folders: RING; RIO) (Box 1206)
    - Ripple, Jimmy (Baseball) - Ritter, Warren W/ (Patomac Bank and Trust) (Collective Folders: RIP; RIS; RIT) (Box 1207)
    - Ritter, Willis (Judge) - Rivlin, Alice Dr. (HFW) (Collective Folders: RIV) (Box 1208)
    - Rixey, Eppa ( Baseball Player) - Robards, Jason Jr. and Sr. (Actor) (Collective Folders: RIZ; RO; ROB) (Box 1209)
    - Robarts, John (Ontario Premier) - Robb, Charles ( Mrs.) (Visits Hawaii 1968) (Collective Folders: ROBBINS; ROBB; ROBE) (Box 1210)
    - Robb, Gene (President - ANPA) - Roberto, Holden (Angola - Official) (Collective Folders: WAH; WAI) (Box 1211)
    - Robert Wagner (Actor) - Waitt Alden H (Major American Chemical Society) (Box 1211)
    - Roberts, Alton ( and Raymond) - Roberts, Richard (Singer) (Collective Folders: ROBERTS A-F; ROBERTS G-I; ROBERTS M-R) (Box 1212)
    - Roberts, Robin (Baseball Player) - Robertson, George W. ( R. E. Board) (Collective Folders: ROBERTS S-Z; ROBERTSON) (Box 1213)
    - Robertson, Isiah - Robinson, Bill (Dancer) (Collective Folders: ROBI; ROBINSON A; ROBINSON B) (Box 1215)
    - Robinson, Brooks (Baseball) - Robinson, Frank (Baseball) (Collective Folders: ROBINSON C; ROBINSON D; ROBINSON E; ROBINSON F) (Box 1216)
    - Robinson, Hamilton - Robinson, Max (TV) (Collective Folders: ROBINSON G; ROBINSON H; ROBINSON I; ROBINSON J; ROBINSON K; ROBINSON L; ROBINSON M) (Box 1217)
    - Robinson, Pearl Thurber Mrs. (Teacher) - Roby, Maud P. Mrs. (School Teacher) (Collective Folders: ROBINSON N; ROBINSON O; ROBINSON P; ROBINSON S; ROBINSON T; ROBINSON U; ROBINSON V; ROBINSON W; ROBIS; ROBS; ROBY) (Box 1218)
    - Roc, Patricia - Rockefeller, John D. III (Collective Folders: ROC; ROCH; ROK) (Box 1219)
    - Rockefeller, John D. IV - Rockefeller, Nelson (Campaign for Gov.1970) (Box 1220)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson ( wire potraits) - Rockefeller, Nelson (with aides, advisors, assistants) (Box 1221)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson (campaigning fo Presidential nomination 1963-1964) - Rockefeller, Nelson (Homes - Vice Presidential) (Box 1222)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson (with Congressmen) - Rockefeller, Winthrop (Gov. Elect of Arkansas) (Box 1223)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop Mrs. - Rodes, Milton (District Motor Vehicles) (Collective Folders: ROD; RODD; RODE) (Box 1224)
    - Rodgers, Andre (Baseball NY Giants) - Rodolph, Katy (Olympic Skier) (Collective Folders: RODG; RODI) (Box 1225)
    - Rodriguez, A. (Baseball Player) - Rogell, William (Baseball) (Collective Folders: RODR; ROE; ROG) (Box 1226)
    - Rogers, Alan (Coach) - Rogers, Harold J. ( States Attorney Maryland) (Collective Folders: ROGERS A-I) (Box 1227)
    - Rogers, James (Mrs.) - Rogers, Will Jr. (Collective Folders: ROGERS J-R; ROGERS S-Z) (Box 1228)
    - Rogers, William (Dept. of Interior) - Rogers, William (Visits India 1972) (Box 1229)
    - Rogers, William (P Visits Japan) - Rogovin, Sol (Baseball) (Box 1230)
    - Rohatyn, Felix G. - Basketball NBA (Rollins, Wayne "The Tree") (Box 1231)
    - Rolling Stones (Musical Group) Star Photos (Walter Oates) 1972 1978 - Rometsch, Elle (W. German Beauty) (Box 1232)
    - Romiti, Philip (Judge) - Romney, George (Speaking) (Box 1233)
    - Romney, George (Visits Slums, Schools, Cities. Etc.) - Romulo, Carlos (Gen. and Wife) (Collective Folders: ROM 1; ROM 2; ROM 3) (Box 1234)
      First folder heavily curled; rusting paperclips throughout
    - Ronan, William (MTA Head) - Roosa, Stuart (MRS.) (Collective Folders: RON; ROO; ROONEY) (Box 1235)
    - Roosevelt, Anna (See: Halstead James) - Roosevelt Franklin D. (Homes - Shangri La) (Box 1236)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D (Monuments and Memorials) - Roosevelt, Franklin D (Mrs. Eleanor 1930's) (Box 1237)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D (Mrs. Eleanor 1940's) - Roosevelt, Franklin D. Jr lll (Box 1238)
    - Roosevelt, James (Congressman) - Roots, Nelson C. (President Civic Association) (Box 1239)
    - Roper, Daniel and Family ((Deceased 4-12-43) - Rose Paul (Canada Crime Suspect) (Collective Folders: ROP; ROR, ROS, ROSE) (Box 1240)
    - Rose, Pete (Baseball Player) - Rosen, Sol W (Box 1241)
    - Rosenberg, Anna (Fomer Dept of Defense Ass't) - Rosenwald, Lessing J (Deceased) (Collective Folders: ROSENB; ROSENF; ROSENTHAL) (Box 1242)
    - Rosewall, Ken (Tennis Ace) - Ross, Robert Tripp (Collective Folders: ROSS A-B; ROSS C; ROSS D; ROSS E-G; ROSS H; ROSS I-L; ROSS M; ROSS R; ROSS; ROSS N-Q) (Box 1243)
    - Ross, Stanford G. (Commisioner of Social Service) - Rostropovich, Mstislav (Cellist) (Collective Folders: ROSS; S; ROSS T; ROSS U-W; ROSS E; ROSS I; ROST) (Box 1244)
    - Rote, Robin (Football) - Rothenberger, Annaliese (Actress) (Collective Folders: ROT; ROTH A-I; ROTH J-R; ROTH S-Z; ROTHE) (Box 1245)
    - Rothman, Stuart - Roush, J. Edward (Rep. D- IND) (Collective Folders: ROU; ROUS) (Box 1246)
    - Roussel, Tom (Football Player) - Rowicki,Witold (Polish Conductor) (Collective Folders: ROV; ROW; ROWE) (Box 1247)
    - Rowland, Betty (golfer) - Rubadini, James (Malawi Amb.) (Collective Folders: ROWL; ROX; ROY; ROZ; RURUB) (Box 1248)
      Some photos with bent corners
    - Rubel, John, M. (Department of Defense) - Rubenstein, Serge (Collective Folders: RUBIN) (Box 1249)
    - Rubio, Euripedes Jr. (USA Medal of Honor Award) - Rudel, Julius (Conductor) (Collective Folders: RUC; RUD) (Box 1250)
    - Rudie, Evelyn (Child Actress) - Rulon, Watson B, Jr. (Hogates) (Collective Folders: RUE; RUF; RUG; RUH; RUI; RUK; RUL) (Box 1251)
    - Rumania (Royal Family Carol King) - Rumsfled, Donald (MRS) (Collective Folders: RUM) (Box 1252)
      Legal MS Box
    - Runcie, Robert Archbishop -Rushworth, Robert A. Capt (Us Air Force) (Collective Folders: RUN; RUP; RUS; RUSH) (Box 1253)
    - Rusie, Amos - Rusk, Dean (Portraits) (Box 1254)
    - Rusk, Dean (Recreation) - Rusk, Dean (Visits Viet Nam 1964) (Box 1255)
    - Rusk, Dean Mrs - Russell, Henry E. (Rev.) (Collective Folders: RUS; RUSSELL A) (Box 1256)
    - Russell, James - Russell, Richard (Box 1257)
    - Russell, Rosalind - Rutherford (Box 1258)
    - Ryan, James P (Realtor) - Ryun Jim Miler (Collective Folders: RYAN JR: RYAN SEC.2, RZ) (Box 1259)
    - Rutigliano - Ryan, Irene (Box 1260)
    - Saad - Sacks (Box 1261)
    - Sadat, Anwar EL 1974 - Sadat Anwar EL (United Arab Republic) (Box 1262)
    - Sadat, Anwar Visits (Israel 1977) - Saenz, Leo (Boxer) (Box 1263)
    - Safdie, Moshe (Architect) - St. Clair, Bob (Football) (Collective Folders: SAF; SAG; SAH; SAINT) (Box 1264)
    - Saint Aubin - Saito, Shizuo (Box 1265)
    - Sakata, Harold (Actor) - Salgada, Plinio (Collective Folders: SAK; SAL; SALE) (Box 1266)
    - Salim, Salim (Tanzania) - Salonen, Neil (Collective Folders: SALI; SALL) (Box 1267)
    - Salter, Bryant (Football Player) - Samuelson, Paul A. (Professor of Economics MIT National Symposium on Inflation 2/9/66) (Collective Folders: SALT; SAM; SAMP; SAMU) (Box 1268)
    - Sanborn, Merrell - Sanders, Clayton (Peoples Drug Stores) (Collective Folders: SAN; SANCHEZ; SAND; SANDE) (Box 1269)
    - Sanders, Doug (Golf) - Sandys, Duncan and Mrs. (Collective Folders: SAND F) (Box 1270)
    - Sanford, George Edward - Santios, Kimberly (Collective Folders: SANF; SANDG; SANT) (Box 1271)
    - Santos, Ron (Baseball) - Saroyan, William (Collective Folders: SAP; SAR; SARGENT; SARL; SARN) (Box 1272)
    - Sarrazin, Michael (Actor) - Saudi Arabia (Abdulla Paisal - Prince) (Collective Folders: SASS; SAT; SATT; SAU) (Box 1273)
    - Saudi Arabia (Royal Family Faisal IBN Musaed IBN Abul) - Saunders, Clarence (Collective Folders: SAUN) (Box 1274)
    - Saunders, Edward E (DC School Board Candidate) - Sawtelle Mathew (Finance) (Collective Folders: SAV; SAW) (Box 1275)
    - Sawyer, Charles (Diplomat) - Saylor John P (Collective Folders: SAX) (Box 1276)
    - Sayre Jr Rev Francis B - SCH+ (Collective Folders: SAY: SC; SCAN; SCAR) (Box 1277)
    - Schact, Al (Baseball comedian) - Schawlow, Arthur (Collective Folders: SCHAF; SCHAL; SCHAR) (Box 1278)
    - Schearer, Hugh Lawson (Prime Minsiter of Jamaica) - Scherrer, Jean - Louis (Designer) (Collective Folders: SCHE; SCHEM) (Box 1279)
    - Scheuer, James H - Schirra, Walter Sr. (Collective Folders: SCHI) (Box 1280)
    - Schisal, Murray (Playright) - Schmertz, Hertbert (fed. Meditation and Conciliation) (Collective Folders: SCHL; SCHLI; SCHM; SCHME) (Box 1281)
    - Schmick, Paul M (Old Man Photgrapher) - Schnabl, Karl (skier) (Collective Folders: SCHMI; SCHMIDT; SCHMIT; SCHN) (Box 1282)
    - Schnabel, Geo. E. REV - Scholz, Robert O (Union Trust Co) (Collective Folders: SCHNEI; SCHO; SCHOL) (Box 1283)
    - Schomberg, Arthur A - Schuetz, Kalus (W. Berlin Senator) (Collective Folders: SCHR; SCHRO; SCHU) (Box 1284)
    - Schuiling, William J. (First National Bank Officer) - Schwable, Frank H. (Col.) (Collective Folders: SCHUUL; SCHULT; SCHULTZ; SCHULZ; SCHUM; SCHUR) (Box 1285)
    - Schwall, Don (Baseball) - Schweinhaut, Margaret (MD. Pol.) (Collective Folders: SCHWARTZ; SCHWARZ; SCHWE) (Box 1286)
    - Schweitzer, Albert (Dr.) - Schwinger, Julian Prof. (Nobel Prize Winner) (Box 1287)